<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PawCenter</string>
    <string name="vaccination_info">Only check this if your pet has undergone core vaccines vital to all pets based on risk of exposure, severity of disease or transmissibility to humans.</string>
    <string name="register_success_dialog">Account created successfully,\n you can now proceed with signing in</string>
    <string name="appointment_success_dialog">Your appointment request has been submited, you will be notified when processed</string>

    <string name="terms_of_use">1. TERMS OF USE
By downloading, browsing, accessing or using this Sample Store mobile application (“Mobile Application”), you agree to be bound by these Terms and Conditions of Use. We reserve the right to amend these terms and conditions at any time. If you disagree with any of these Terms and Conditions of Use, you must immediately discontinue your access to the Mobile Application and your use of the services offered on the Mobile Application. Continued use of the Mobile Application will constitute acceptance of these Terms and Conditions of Use, as may be amended from time to time.

2. DEFINITIONS
In these Terms and Conditions of Use, the following capitalised terms shall have the following meanings, except where the context otherwise requires:

"Account" means an account created by a User on the Mobile Application as part of Registration.

"Merchant" refers to any entity whose products or Samples can be purchased and/or redeemed (as the case may be) via the Mobile Application.

"Privacy Policy" means the privacy policy set out in Clause 14 of these Terms and Conditions of Use.

"Redeem" means to redeem a Merchant’s products or Samples on these Terms and Conditions of Use and

"Redemption" means the act of redeeming such products or Samples.

"Register" means to create an Account on the Mobile Application and "Registration" means the act of creating such an Account.

"Samples" means samples of Merchant’s products and/or Merchant’s services, including without limitation, any vouchers for the redemption of such services, and "Sample" means any one of them.

"Services" means all the services provided by Singapore Post Limited via the Mobile Application to Users, and "Service" means any one of them,

"Users" means users of the Mobile Application, including you and "User" means any one of them.

3. GENERAL ISSUES ABOUT THE MOBILE APPLICATION AND THE SERVICES
3.1 Applicability of terms and conditions: The use of any Services and/or the Mobile Application and the making of any Redemptions are subject to these Terms and Conditions of Use.

3.2 Location: The Mobile Application, the Services and any Redemptions are intended solely for use by Users who access the Mobile Application in Singapore. We make no representation that the Services (or any goods or services) are available or otherwise suitable for use outside of Singapore. Notwithstanding the above, if you access the Mobile Application, use the Services or make any Redemptions from locations outside Singapore, you do so on your own initiative and are responsible for the consequences and for compliance with all applicable laws.

3.3 Scope: The Mobile Application, the Services and any Redemptions are for your non-commercial, personal use only and must not be used for business purposes.

3.4 Prevention on use: We reserve the right to prevent you using the Mobile Application and the Service (or any part of them) and to prevent you from making any Redemptions.

3.5 Equipment and Networks: The provision of the Services and the Mobile Application does not include the provision of a mobile telephone or handheld device or other necessary equipment to access the Mobile Application or the Services or make any Redemptions. To use the Mobile Application or Services or to make Redemptions, you will require Internet connectivity and appropriate telecommunication links. You acknowledge that the terms of agreement with your respective mobile network provider ("Mobile Provider") will continue to apply when using the Mobile Application. As a result, you may be charged by the Mobile Provider for access to network connection services for the duration of the connection while accessing the Mobile Application or any such third party charges as may arise. You accept responsibility for any such charges that arise.

3.6 Permission to use Mobile Application: If you are not the bill payer for the mobile telephone or handheld device being used to access the Mobile Application, you will be assumed to have received permission from the bill payer for using the Mobile Application.

3.7 License to Use Material: By submitting any text or images (including photographs) (“Material”) via the Application, you represent that you are the owner of the Material, or have proper authorization from the owner of the Material to use, reproduce and distribute it. You hereby grant us a worldwide, royalty-free, non-exclusive license to use the Material to promote any products or services.

4. REDEMPTIONS
4.1 Need for registration: You must Register to make a Redemption from the Mobile Application.

4.2 Application of these Terms and Conditions of Use: By making any Redemption, you acknowledge that the Redemption is subject to these Terms and Conditions of Use.

4.3 Redemption: Any attempted Redemption not consistent with these Terms and Conditions of Use may be disallowed or rendered void at our or the relevant Merchant’s discretion.

4.4 Responsibility for Redemptions of perishable products of Samples: Each Merchant shall be responsible to ensure that any of its products or Samples for Redemption that are perishable has not expired.

4.5 Restrictions: (a) Reproduction, sale, resale or trading of any products or Samples or Redeemed products is prohibited. (b) If any product or Sample is Redeemed for less than its face value, there is no entitlement to a credit, cash or Sample equal to the difference between the face value and the amount Redeemed. (c) Redemption of products or Samples is subject to availability of the relevant Merchants’ stocks.

4.6 SingPost Not Liable: For the avoidance of doubt, Singapore Post Limited shall not be liable for any losses or damages suffered by you resulting from a failure by the relevant Merchant to fulfil any Redemptions in accordance with Clause 4.4 or for a failure by us to deliver any products or Samples to you due to the unavailability of such products or Samples pursuant to Clause 4.5(c).</string>
</resources>
